<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pets on i94card</title>
    <link>https://i94card.com/tags/pets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pets on i94card</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://i94card.com/tags/pets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extraverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 2 of a Two-Part Series</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-2-of-a-two-part-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-2-of-a-two-part-series/</guid>
      <description>Why do we love Disney characters so much? What is it about their stories that touches our hearts?
We see reflections of own personalities in characters like Jiminy Cricket, Alice in Wonderland, Pocahontas, and even Merlin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Was Donald Trump’s Mother? Mary Anne MacLeod Trump</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/mary-anne-macleod-trump-donald-trumps-mother/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/mary-anne-macleod-trump-donald-trumps-mother/</guid>
      <description>The Foundations of Greatness: Exploring the Early Life and Background of Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Parents The story of a prominent figure often finds its roots in the experiences and influences of their parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You a Sensor or an Intuitive?</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/are-you-a-sensor-or-an-intuitive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/are-you-a-sensor-or-an-intuitive/</guid>
      <description>More confusion probably exists regarding Sensors (S) and Intuitives (N) than any other type. Extraverts (E) and Introverts (I) are easy to tell apart. So are Thinkers (T) and Feelers (F).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droid Addiction</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/droid-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/droid-addiction/</guid>
      <description>At an upscale restaurant with two women friends the other night, I watched one play with her android nonstop during dinner. She showed us over 100 photos taken with several cameras on the device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Cost of Meat</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/environmental-cost-of-meat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/environmental-cost-of-meat/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. could feed 800 million people with grain that livestock consume say Cornell University ecologist researchers. If the grain were exported, it would increase the U.S. trade balance by $80 billion per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extraverts in Retirement</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverts-in-retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverts-in-retirement/</guid>
      <description>With advancing age, their Myers-Briggs personality scores of people can change, but not by much. Extreme scores on one or more traits tend to soften and move toward the middle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally, an Updated Version of the Big Book of AA for Today’s Reader</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/ez-big-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/ez-big-book/</guid>
      <description>The EZ Big Book of Alcoholics Anonymous is a paragraph by paragraph “translation” of the original Alcoholics Anonymous—known to AA members as the Big Book—published by AA founder Bill Wilson in the 1930s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Seduce an INFJ Woman</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/how-to-seduce-an-infj-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/how-to-seduce-an-infj-woman/</guid>
      <description>The way that men and women express themselves in love matches differs widely. Much of the difference can be traced back to Myers-Briggs type. Some types are more sexual than others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ENFJ</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-enfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-enfj/</guid>
      <description>People of the INFJ and ENFJ Myers-Briggs types usually make compatible friends and partners. It makes sense when you look at their shared traits: intuition, feeling, and judging. The two types differ only in their tendencies toward introversion and extraversion, and that’s not all bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ENTP</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-entp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-entp/</guid>
      <description>INFJs usually get along well with ENTPs. This may be surprising when one considers that they have only one Myers-Briggs trait in common—intuition (N).
With their tendency toward introversion (I), INFJs are reserved and shy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets ESTP</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-estp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-estp/</guid>
      <description>When an INFJ meets an ESTP, some special chemistry must be at work for them to enjoy time together. These Myers-Briggs types are exact opposites. The INFJ (I) is introverted—a private person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFJ Meets INFP</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-infp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-infp/</guid>
      <description>INFP (introverted-intuitive-feeling-perceiving) and INFJ (introverted-intuitive-feeling-judging) types are a lot alike. They have rich inner lives and treasure their solitude. Also, their intuition is highly developed, giving them the ability to see what’s going on under the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introverts at Risk</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/introverts-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/introverts-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>Each of the sixteen Myers-Briggs types is unique and different. Some types are outgoing and gregarious, while others treasure their privacy. Some are serious and others are fun-loving. Some are warm and giving and others are cool-headed and objective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air?  INFJ Meets INFP</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infp/</guid>
      <description>INFP and INFJ types are alike in many ways. Both types are introverted (I), intuitive (N), and feeling (F). They have rich inner lives and treasure their solitude. Their intuition is highly developed, giving them the ability to see what’s going on under the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ENFP</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-enfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-enfp/</guid>
      <description>Myers-Briggs personality traits have a lot to do with the potential for romance, friendship, and working relationships. They’re important in family life, too. Romance has a better chance of lasting between lovers of similar Myers-Briggs types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets INFJ</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infj/</guid>
      <description>When two INFJs find each other, they’re lucky. After all, only one percent of the population is the INFJ type. INFJs are kind, generous, and helpful to others. When friends or even strangers are in trouble, INFJs hurry to the rescue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ISTP</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-istp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-istp/</guid>
      <description>If you’re an INFJ, you may find yourself drawn to ISTPs. They’re quietly competent, people of few words who make every utterance worth listening to. They pay attention. They have emotional control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Johari’s Window</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/joharis-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/joharis-window/</guid>
      <description>The Johari Window is a psychological model that was designed for use in self-help groups to help members become more intimate with their peers, while at the same time learning to become more honest with themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types of Children—Extraverted Kids</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-extraverted-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-extraverted-kids/</guid>
      <description>Do children’s personalities remain consistent over the years? If they’re happy babies, will they be happy adults? Or do experiences early in life play a major role in what they become?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types of Children—Part 1: Introverted Kids</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-part-1-introverted-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-part-1-introverted-kids/</guid>
      <description>If your baby comes home from the hospital quiet and easy-going, will the peace last? What about the toddler who enjoys nothing more than turning the pages of a book, while another is scaling every surface in sight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year’s Resolutions for INFJs</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/am/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/am/</guid>
      <description>We INFJs, like the other fifteen Myers-Briggs types, have our weak spots—vulnerabilities that sometimes bring us into conflict with others or cause personal problems. To be healthy and fully functional, we need to take advantage of all eight Myers-Briggs traits: introvert (I), extravert (E), sensing (S), intuitive (N), thinking (T), feeling (F), judging (J), and perceiving (P).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prevalence of INFJs in the General Population</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/prevalence-of-infjs-in-the-general-population/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/prevalence-of-infjs-in-the-general-population/</guid>
      <description>According to researchers, the INFJ Myers-Briggs type occurs in about 1% of the population—the lowest prevalence of any type. Studies vary regarding the exact percentages of the 16 types, but INFJs always walk away with the prize for the most rare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTD in INFJ Women After Sexual Assault</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/pstd-in-infj-women-after-sexual-assault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/pstd-in-infj-women-after-sexual-assault/</guid>
      <description>Several readers have asked whether INFJ women are more prone than other Myers-Briggs types to getting PTSD after sexual assault. The readers have themselves been victims of rape. I’d never considered this idea before, but I think they’re onto something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanja Askani–Creator of the New Bambi and Thumper</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/tanja-askani-creator-of-the-new-bambi-and-thumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/tanja-askani-creator-of-the-new-bambi-and-thumper/</guid>
      <description>Return of Bambi and Thumper
Tanja Askani, a Czech author, photographer, and animal scientist living in Germany, has disseminated a series of Bambi-Thumper photos that have gone viral on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blame Game</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/the-blame-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/the-blame-game/</guid>
      <description>Are you prone to playing the “blame game” when something goes wrong in your life? Do you have friends or relatives who do it? There are lots of synonyms for “blame”—for example, “hold responsible or accountable”, “condemn,” “accuse,” “find guilty,” “assign fault,” or even “point the finger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lord’s Prayer in A.A. Meetings</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/the-lords-prayer-in-a-a-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/the-lords-prayer-in-a-a-meetings/</guid>
      <description>In my AA home group, we start meetings by reading from the Big Book: “AA is not allied with any sect, denomination, politics, organization, or institution.” Then we end with the Lord’s Prayer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timex or Rolex?</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/timex-or-rolex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/timex-or-rolex/</guid>
      <description>Timex, hands down. Please understand, I don’t have a grudge against Rolex watches because I can’t afford one–although, at an average price of $8000, it would pinch a little. I like the way the Timex looks–modest, practical, tasteful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Waits, I Love You</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/tom-waits-i-love-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/tom-waits-i-love-you/</guid>
      <description>Only this year, after my 78th birthday, did I discover Tom Waits. Now I’m in love and it’s too late. Tom is probably happily married and too old for this, anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unconditional Love</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/unconditional-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/unconditional-love/</guid>
      <description>Animals are such agreeable friends. They ask no questions. They pass no criticisms. —George Eliot
If you have a dog or cat you’re close to, you know what unconditional love is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When INFJs Go Bad</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/when-infjs-go-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/when-infjs-go-bad/</guid>
      <description>When INFJs are on track, they’re creative and insightful. They’re almost clairvoyant. In addition, they’re compassionate and generous. They are protectors of the weak. As idealists, they have strong values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Study Habits</title>
      <link>https://i94card.com/wp/your-study-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i94card.com/wp/your-study-habits/</guid>
      <description>In fifty years of solitary work—researching and writing—I’ve discovered that some environments put me in a more productive frame of mind than others. When the conditions aren’t “ideal” for me, I get distracted easily.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
