<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BeaconStreet USA</title><link>https://i94card.com/</link><description>Recent content on BeaconStreet USA</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://i94card.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Free Myers Briggs Type Indicator MBTI Test</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/free-myers-briggs-type-indicator-mbti-test/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/free-myers-briggs-type-indicator-mbti-test/</guid><description>The MBTI stands for Myers-Briggs Type Indicator. It is an assessment of personality based on questions about a person’s preferences in four domains: focusing outward or inward; attending to sensory information or adding interpretation; deciding by logic or by situation; and making judgments or remaining open to information1.</description></item><item><title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types—Part 1: The Extraverts</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-1-the-extraverts/</guid><description>In recent years, Myers-Briggs experts have analyzed many famous people to make educated guesses of their personality types. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.</description></item><item><title>INFJ meets ENTJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-entj/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-entj/</guid><description>INFJs and ENTJs are on the same wavelength in many ways. They enjoy spending time together and sharing creative, stimulating conversations.</description></item><item><title>Extraverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 2 of a Two-Part Series</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-2-of-a-two-part-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-2-of-a-two-part-series/</guid><description>Why do we love Disney characters so much? What is it about their stories that touches our hearts?
We see reflections of own personalities in characters like Jiminy Cricket, Alice in Wonderland, Pocahontas, and even Merlin.</description></item><item><title>Famous Infjs The Good And The Evil!</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/famous-infjs-the-good-and-the-evil/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/famous-infjs-the-good-and-the-evil/</guid><description>Famous Good amd Evil INFJ people
INFJ is one of the 16 personality types identified by the Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI).</description></item><item><title>Introverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 1 of a Two-Part Series</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/introverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-1-of-a-two-part-series/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/introverted-disney-characters-and-their-personality-types-part-1-of-a-two-part-series/</guid><description>Introverted Disney Characters and Their Personality Types: Part 1 of a Two-Part Series
Why do Disney characters hold such a special place in our hearts?</description></item><item><title>Extroverted Animals And Their Myers Briggs Personality Types!</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:47 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</guid><description>The Extroverted Myers-Briggs Personality Type: Animals, Traits, and Identification
The Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI) is a popular psychological assessment tool that categorizes individuals into 16 distinct personality types based on their preferences and tendencies.</description></item><item><title>Introverted Reserved Animals and their myers briggs personality types</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/introverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:09:47 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/introverted-animals-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types/</guid><description>The Introverted Myers Briggs Personality : Shy And Quiet Type
Exploring Animal Examples and Identifying Traits
The Myers Briggs Personality Type Indicator (MBTI) is a popular tool used to categorize individuals based on their psychological preferences.</description></item><item><title>Who Was Donald Trump’s Mother? Mary Anne MacLeod Trump</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/mary-anne-macleod-trump-donald-trumps-mother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/mary-anne-macleod-trump-donald-trumps-mother/</guid><description>The Foundations of Greatness: Exploring the Early Life and Background of Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Parents The story of a prominent figure often finds its roots in the experiences and influences of their parents.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ISTJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-istj-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-istj-2/</guid><description>It’s fair to say that any two people with this combination of Myers-Briggs traits are likely to have adjustment problems if they’re to function smoothly together.</description></item><item><title>Career Distribution by Myers-Briggs Type</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-type-and-career-choice/</guid><description>A 14-year study of thousands of Americans in various careers shows that different Myers-Biggs types have different preferences and skills relating to the jobs they take.</description></item><item><title>Depression Profiles—INFJ vs. INFP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/depression-profiles-infj-vs-infp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/depression-profiles-infj-vs-infp/</guid><description>The Myers-Briggs types INFJ and INFP are affected by depression more than most other types. Both are Introverted (I), intuitive (N), and feeling (F).</description></item><item><title>Famous People and Their Myers-Briggs Personality Types: Part 2, the Introverts</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/famous-people-and-their-myers-briggs-personality-types-part-2-the-introverts/</guid><description>The Myers-Briggs personality test has been used to analyze many famous people. While most celebrities, past and present, have never taken a personality test, psychologists who are knowledgeable about typology believe they know what the outcomes would be.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ESFJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-esfj/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-esfj/</guid><description>When an INFJ and ESFJ are drawn to each other, the attraction becomes obvious fairly quickly— although the ESFJ is usually the more transparent of the two and is likely to make the first overtures.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ESFP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-esfp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-esfp/</guid><description>What happens when an INFJ meets an ESFP? Is there an instant attraction? Do they repel each other like two magnets?</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ESTJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-estj-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-estj-2/</guid><description>All things considered, the attraction between the ESTJs and INFJs isn’t surprising. Because ESTJs are conventional people, they prefer colorful partners to make their lives more interesting.</description></item><item><title>INFJ meets INTP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-intp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-intp/</guid><description>INFJs are often drawn to INTPs because of their intelligence and ability to apply logic to every situation. Eventually, though, INFJs tend to find most INTPs distant because of their unemotional approach to life.</description></item><item><title>INFJ meets ISFJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-isfj/</guid><description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. They’re introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ISFP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-isfp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-isfp/</guid><description>As one of sixteen Myers-Briggs types, the INFJ is introverted (I), intuitive (N), feeling (F), and judging (J). A little different from the ISFP—who shares the introverted (I) and feeling (F) traits but not the intuitive (N) and judging (J) traits.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ISTP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-istp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-istp/</guid><description>It’s obvious looking at the letters I-N-F-J and I-S-T-P that these two Myers-Briggs personality types are very different. The only trait they have in common is their introversion.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Men as Lovers</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-men-as-lovers/</guid><description>INFJ men are complex, warm, and perceptive. They’re drawn to women who are intelligent, creative, and compassionate. While few INFJ men ever achieve perfect relationships, they always wish for them.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Women as Lovers</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-women-as-lovers/</guid><description>The INFJ female is an intense, passionate woman. She is drawn to the opposite sex, but few of them turn out to be long-term partners because they’re the wrong type.</description></item><item><title>INFJs smile</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infjs-smile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infjs-smile/</guid><description>In days when it seems hard to be an INFJ, it’s worth looking at some of the qualities that come with this Myers-Briggs personality type.</description></item><item><title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ISFJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-isfj/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-isfj/</guid><description>INFJs and ISFJs are alike in many ways. Both are introverted, feeling, and judging. They differ only on the intuitive/sensing (N/S) dimension of the Myers-Briggs Inventory.</description></item><item><title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ—The Rarest Myers-Briggs Personality Type</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj/</guid><description>Myers-Briggs Inventory
Isabel Myers and her mother, Katharine Briggs—both psychologists— developed the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory more than fifty years ago.</description></item><item><title>It’s Hard To Be an INFJ: The Author’s Personal Story</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/its-hard-to-be-an-infj-the-authors-personal-story/</guid><description>Since posting “It’s Hard To Be an INFJ” on this blog, I’ve received hundreds of e-mails from other INFJs. Their main theme has been how disconnected they’ve felt surrounded by extraverts and more sensible, earthbound types.</description></item><item><title>Perceiving vs. Judging—The Dating Game</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/perceiving-vs-judging-the-conflict/</guid><description>Perceiving (P) and Judging (J) are a set of opposite traits on the Myers-Briggs Personality Inventory. They are called the attitude traits.</description></item><item><title>Sensors vs. Intuitives—The Dating Game</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:10:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/sensors-vs-intuitives-the-dating-game/</guid><description>In the dating game, the Sensing and Intuitive Myers-Briggs preferences can be a source of excitement and, at the same time, confusion.</description></item><item><title>Are You a Sensor or an Intuitive?</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/are-you-a-sensor-or-an-intuitive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/are-you-a-sensor-or-an-intuitive/</guid><description>More confusion probably exists regarding Sensors (S) and Intuitives (N) than any other type. Extraverts (E) and Introverts (I) are easy to tell apart.</description></item><item><title>Droid Addiction</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/droid-addiction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/droid-addiction/</guid><description>At an upscale restaurant with two women friends the other night, I watched one play with her android nonstop during dinner.</description></item><item><title>Environmental Cost of Meat</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/environmental-cost-of-meat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/environmental-cost-of-meat/</guid><description>The U.S. could feed 800 million people with grain that livestock consume say Cornell University ecologist researchers. If the grain were exported, it would increase the U.</description></item><item><title>Extraverts in Retirement</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverts-in-retirement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/extraverts-in-retirement/</guid><description>With advancing age, their Myers-Briggs personality scores of people can change, but not by much. Extreme scores on one or more traits tend to soften and move toward the middle.</description></item><item><title>Finally, an Updated Version of the Big Book of AA for Today’s Reader</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/ez-big-book/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/ez-big-book/</guid><description>The EZ Big Book of Alcoholics Anonymous is a paragraph by paragraph “translation” of the original Alcoholics Anonymous—known to AA members as the Big Book—published by AA founder Bill Wilson in the 1930s.</description></item><item><title>How To Seduce an INFJ Woman</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/how-to-seduce-an-infj-woman/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/how-to-seduce-an-infj-woman/</guid><description>The way that men and women express themselves in love matches differs widely. Much of the difference can be traced back to Myers-Briggs type.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ENFJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-enfj/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-enfj/</guid><description>People of the INFJ and ENFJ Myers-Briggs types usually make compatible friends and partners. It makes sense when you look at their shared traits: intuition, feeling, and judging.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ENTP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-entp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-entp/</guid><description>INFJs usually get along well with ENTPs. This may be surprising when one considers that they have only one Myers-Briggs trait in common—intuition (N).</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets ESTP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-estp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-estp/</guid><description>When an INFJ meets an ESTP, some special chemistry must be at work for them to enjoy time together. These Myers-Briggs types are exact opposites.</description></item><item><title>INFJ Meets INFP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-infp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/infj-meets-infp/</guid><description>INFP (introverted-intuitive-feeling-perceiving) and INFJ (introverted-intuitive-feeling-judging) types are a lot alike. They have rich inner lives and treasure their solitude. Also, their intuition is highly developed, giving them the ability to see what’s going on under the surface.</description></item><item><title>Introverts at Risk</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/introverts-at-risk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/introverts-at-risk/</guid><description>Each of the sixteen Myers-Briggs types is unique and different. Some types are outgoing and gregarious, while others treasure their privacy.</description></item><item><title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets INFP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infp/</guid><description>INFP and INFJ types are alike in many ways. Both types are introverted (I), intuitive (N), and feeling (F). They have rich inner lives and treasure their solitude.</description></item><item><title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ENFP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-enfp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-enfp/</guid><description>Myers-Briggs personality traits have a lot to do with the potential for romance, friendship, and working relationships. They’re important in family life, too.</description></item><item><title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets INFJ</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infj/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-infj/</guid><description>When two INFJs find each other, they’re lucky. After all, only one percent of the population is the INFJ type.</description></item><item><title>Is Romance in the Air? INFJ Meets ISTP</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-istp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/is-romance-in-the-air-infj-meets-istp/</guid><description>If you’re an INFJ, you may find yourself drawn to ISTPs. They’re quietly competent, people of few words who make every utterance worth listening to.</description></item><item><title>Johari’s Window</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/joharis-window/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/joharis-window/</guid><description>The Johari Window is a psychological model that was designed for use in self-help groups to help members become more intimate with their peers, while at the same time learning to become more honest with themselves.</description></item><item><title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types of Children—Extraverted Kids</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-extraverted-kids/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-extraverted-kids/</guid><description>Do children’s personalities remain consistent over the years? If they’re happy babies, will they be happy adults? Or do experiences early in life play a major role in what they become?</description></item><item><title>Myers-Briggs Personality Types of Children—Part 1: Introverted Kids</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-part-1-introverted-kids/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/myers-briggs-personality-types-of-children-part-1-introverted-kids/</guid><description>If your baby comes home from the hospital quiet and easy-going, will the peace last? What about the toddler who enjoys nothing more than turning the pages of a book, while another is scaling every surface in sight?</description></item><item><title>New Gainesville Ketamine Infusion Clinic</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/new-gainesville-ketamine-infusion-clinic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/new-gainesville-ketamine-infusion-clinic/</guid><description>Exploring Shy and Introvert Disney Characters: A Journey Through the Quiet and Reserved
Florida Mind Health Center for Ketamine Therapy is Gainesville’s new—and only—ketamine infusion therapy center.</description></item><item><title>New Year’s Resolutions for INFJs</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/am/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/am/</guid><description>We INFJs, like the other fifteen Myers-Briggs types, have our weak spots—vulnerabilities that sometimes bring us into conflict with others or cause personal problems.</description></item><item><title>Prevalence of INFJs in the General Population</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/prevalence-of-infjs-in-the-general-population/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/prevalence-of-infjs-in-the-general-population/</guid><description>According to researchers, the INFJ Myers-Briggs type occurs in about 1% of the population—the lowest prevalence of any type. Studies vary regarding the exact percentages of the 16 types, but INFJs always walk away with the prize for the most rare.</description></item><item><title>PSTD in INFJ Women After Sexual Assault</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/pstd-in-infj-women-after-sexual-assault/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/pstd-in-infj-women-after-sexual-assault/</guid><description>Several readers have asked whether INFJ women are more prone than other Myers-Briggs types to getting PTSD after sexual assault.</description></item><item><title>Tanja Askani–Creator of the New Bambi and Thumper</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/tanja-askani-creator-of-the-new-bambi-and-thumper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/tanja-askani-creator-of-the-new-bambi-and-thumper/</guid><description>Return of Bambi and Thumper
Tanja Askani, a Czech author, photographer, and animal scientist living in Germany, has disseminated a series of Bambi-Thumper photos that have gone viral on the internet.</description></item><item><title>The Blame Game</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/the-blame-game/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/the-blame-game/</guid><description>Are you prone to playing the “blame game” when something goes wrong in your life? Do you have friends or relatives who do it?</description></item><item><title>The Lord’s Prayer in A.A. Meetings</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/the-lords-prayer-in-a-a-meetings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/the-lords-prayer-in-a-a-meetings/</guid><description>In my AA home group, we start meetings by reading from the Big Book: “AA is not allied with any sect, denomination, politics, organization, or institution.</description></item><item><title>Timex or Rolex?</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/timex-or-rolex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/timex-or-rolex/</guid><description>Timex, hands down. Please understand, I don’t have a grudge against Rolex watches because I can’t afford one–although, at an average price of $8000, it would pinch a little.</description></item><item><title>Tom Waits, I Love You</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/tom-waits-i-love-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/tom-waits-i-love-you/</guid><description>Only this year, after my 78th birthday, did I discover Tom Waits. Now I’m in love and it’s too late.</description></item><item><title>Unconditional Love</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/unconditional-love/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/unconditional-love/</guid><description>Animals are such agreeable friends. They ask no questions. They pass no criticisms. —George Eliot
If you have a dog or cat you’re close to, you know what unconditional love is.</description></item><item><title>When INFJs Go Bad</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/when-infjs-go-bad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/when-infjs-go-bad/</guid><description>When INFJs are on track, they’re creative and insightful. They’re almost clairvoyant. In addition, they’re compassionate and generous. They are protectors of the weak.</description></item><item><title>Your Study Habits</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/your-study-habits/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/your-study-habits/</guid><description>In fifty years of solitary work—researching and writing—I’ve discovered that some environments put me in a more productive frame of mind than others.</description></item><item><title>What Makes Him Want Only You</title><link>https://i94card.com/wp/what-makes-him-want-only-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 01:09:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/wp/what-makes-him-want-only-you/</guid><description>Do you ever get a gut feeling about someone the instant you meet them?
When that happens, you know it’s not because of what they said or did.</description></item><item><title>Aria Fox</title><link>https://i94card.com/authors/aria-fox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/authors/aria-fox/</guid><description>lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostr navigation et dolore magna aliqua.</description></item><item><title>Elements</title><link>https://i94card.com/pages/elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/pages/elements/</guid><description>Table of Contents Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Emphasis Button Link Paragraph Ordered List Unordered List Notice Tab Accordions Code and Syntax Highlighting Blockquote Tables Image Gallery Slider Youtube video Custom video Here is an example of headings.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://i94card.com/pages/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/pages/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy Last updated: September 30, 2023
This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.</description></item><item><title>Ready to build your next project with Hugo?</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item><item><title>Thanks for Joining the Waitlist</title><link>https://i94card.com/pages/thankyou/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://i94card.com/pages/thankyou/</guid><description>Thank You We have added you to the waitlist.
Expect to hear from us shortly.</description></item><item><title>What Users Are Saying About I94card.com</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description/></item></channel></rss>